arit now understands people
arit ahora entiende a las personas
interested in Twitch Oh curious cli
interesadas en Twitch Oh curioso cli
let's see it and in my case for me
vamos a verlo e yo en mi caso para mí
this is more than anything a group of
esto es más que nada un conjunto de
people who can get along better or worse,
gente que se puedan llevar mejor o peor
here there were people that I didn't like
yo aquí había gente que me caía mal
just as there were people that I really liked, those
igual que había gente que me caía de
that I don't like I'm not going
maravilla yo los que me caen mal no voy
to speak to them and those that I
a dirigirles la palabra y los que me
like I'm going to go with them I'm going to
caen bien Voy a ir con ellos les voy a
greet them and it's going to be my moment to
saludar y va a ser mi momento de
take advantage of to say Hey my moment to
aprovechar de decir Oye mi momento de
be with you that is very different than
estar contigo eso es muy diferente que
for example the series live Yes
por ejemplo las series en en directo Sí
yes there is a lot of difference with an
sí que hay mucha diferencia con un
event an event I think it's more with
evento un evento Yo creo que es más con
that excuse of to see each other and such And
la excusa esa de para vernos y tal Y
then the series yes they are made more
luego las series sí que están hechas más
focused on there more individually
enfocadas a a allá más individualmente
because [ __ ] bad vibes are generated that it
porque [__] se generan malos rollos que
's ugly you know and me who comes from being
está feo sabes y yo que vengo de estar
very chill very I don't know what I get into
muy chill muy no sé qué me meto en
Twitter I see so many things that then at
Twitter veo tantas movidas que luego en
home I can say [ __ ] no things you
casa yo puedo decir [__] noas movidas
know like there's one here one I don't know what I don't
sabes en plan hay uno aquí uno no sé qué
know which one and it's also sillo but they
no sé cuál y también es sal sillo pero
don't change especially I've seen it more in
no cambian sobre todo lo he visto más en
the subject of  the girls eh yes it is
el tema de las chicas Eh sí que es
true that we girls get more tired
cierto que nos cansamos más las chicas
than the boys because girls
que los chicos porque las chicas
receive eh
recibimos eh
a very serious harassment very very serious the
un acoso muy gordo muy muy gordo los
others also have eh like I know of
demás también tienen eh en plan yo sé de
people who go to their homes and everything but I do
gente a la que le van a casa y todo pero
n't know why I think that each one of us
no sé por qué yo creo que cada uno
has our own little troubles that
tenemos nuestros propios malitos que nos
haunt us true many times we
persiguen verdad muchas veces nosotros
only realize our
solamente nos damos cuenta de los
own but but in
nuestros pero pero en
reality in reality each one will have their
realidad en realidad cada uno tendrá lo
own thing in the case of girls it is like
suyo en el caso de las chicas es como
very very heavy very very so I think that
muy muy heavy muy muy entonces creo que
in the end it ends up getting a little tiring and and that
al final acaba cansando un poco y Y eso
can also tire people like
también les puede cansar a gente como
ibai or like in the end there will come a point where
ibai o como al final llegará un punto en
if there is so much hate and there is so much
el que si hay tanto odio y hay tanta
[ __ ] it will all end and if it
[__] se va a acabar todo y si se acaba
all ends I assure you that those who lose are those who
todo os aseguro que los que perdéis sois
are inciting hate now more
lo estáis incitando el odio ahora más
than stop liking the role itself what did you
que dejarte de gustar el rol en sí que
see the people who were appearing and
viste la gente que estaba apareciendo y
their intentions Haha the climbers and the
sus intenciones Jaja los trepas y los
so-called Vultures and buas in heat let's call a spade a spade
llamados Buitres y buas en celo digamos
Yes but I have changed
las cosas como son Sí pero he cambiado
my perception a bit about it eh I mean
un poco mi percepción al respecto eh o
my Javi you can  do an
sea mi Javi puedes hacerle una
interview with barb kernes Greetings to the
entrevista a barb kernes Saludos a la
kids and the urones in the
chavaleria y a los urones en el
fire sanctuary To whom who has
santuario fuego A quién a quién me ha
told me can you put my name in the
dicho podéis ponerme el nombre en el
chat what has told me To whom has told me
chat que me ha dicho A quién me ha dicho
that I will do the interview to whom
que le hago la entrevista a quién
put my name in the chat please And
ponerme el nombre en el chat porfa Y
who is perception about it has
quién es percepción al respecto ha
changed a lot and my way of seeing it has
cambiado mucho y mi forma de verlo ha
changed a lot eh And today I see it
cambiado mucho eh Y a día de hoy lo veo
super normal I see it as normal that any
super normal veo normal que cualquier
person having the opportunity to
persona teniendo la oportunidad de
open up being that the role has many
abrirse siendo que el rol tiene muchos
viewers and and and the role moves a lot of
espectadores y y y el rol mueve mucha
people It is very normal that many people
gente Es muy normal que mucha gente
try Barbie kerne a very
intente Barbie kerne un youtuber muy
famous youtuber I don't know who bar vierne is but it is
famoso no sé quién es bar vierne pero es
some type of trolling for sure you are not
algún tipo de troleo seguro no me estáis
taking my click not to make fun of me
cogiendo un click no para burlarse de mí
no and for whatever reason well approach the
no e por lo que sea pues acercarse a la
people who have more numbers or or or what do there
gente que más números tiene o o o que
are people who do it not as the
haga hay gente que lo hace no como las
intentions they simply want the
intenciones simplemente le quieren el
best for themselves and it is legal and it is
bien para ellos mismos y es lícito y es
normal and It is logical you know and and
normal y Es lógico sabes y y
honestly there I have had a
honestamente ahí he tenido un cambio
quite big change of thinking yes it is
bastante grande de pensamiento sí que es
true that before I was like very Nazi
verdad que yo antes era como muy nazi En
In that sense in  plan Lu that I am that well
ese sentido en plan Lu que soy que bueno
I mean I was very born in the
me refiero era eraa muy nac en el
sense that and if I saw that someone
sentido de que e si yo veía que alguien
was very shameless it was already like Cruz you
era muy descarado ya era en plan Cruz
know and today I see it as more like
sabes y a día de hoy lo veo como más en
Okay you can call yourself interested
plan Okay se te puede llamar interesado
but it's normal you know that you are because
pero es normal sabes que lo seas porque
in the end you want your
al final quieres que te suban los
numbers to go up you want those titles we have titles
números quieres ehos título tenemos tít
each one looks out for their own place let's not
cada uno mira por su que no se me olvide
forget that we have a
lugar que no se me olvide que tenemos
title we have a title we
título tenemos título tenemos título
oblige not and well in the end what are you going to
obligo no y pues al final qué vas a
do then I no longer have that
hacer entonces ya no tengo ese
thought that I had before before it was
pensamiento que tenía antes antes era
like very such also in my case
como muy tal también es que en mi caso
For example because I was very lucky
Yo por ejemplo porque tuve mucha suerte
if you notice I mean I will always
yo si os dais cuenta o sea yo siempre lo
say it I had a very big Boom eh
diré yo tuve un Boom muy grande eh
first for being a cute girl because it's
primero por ser una chica mona porque es
true that at that time with cute
cierto que que en ese momento con mona
I don't mean beautiful eh people
no me refiero a a bella eh a la gente le
liked me everyone said oh how cute she is she's pretty Let's
caí bien todo el mundo decía ay qué mona
see she's pretty she's pretty damn she's very pretty
es es guapa A ver es guapa es guapa [__]
someone is very pretty you know
es muy guapa alguien muy guapa es sabes
I'm second because [ __ ] Look at the
soy segundo porque [__] Mirad los
friends I had you know and that I have
amigos que tenía sabes y que tengo
thanks  to God I maintain a good good
gracias a Dios mantengo buena buena
relationship and good friendship with many people
relación y buena amistad con mucha gente
So I will always be in debt
Entonces siempre voy a estar en deuda
Always I will never say no, everything is for
Siempre Nunca voy a decir no yo todo por
me, no because it is not true that later
mí no porque no es verdad que luego
you can maintain more or less there are streaks There are
puedas mantener más menos hay rachas Hay
times when you stop doing
momentos en los que dejas de de hacer
one thing or another, you do better, you do worse
una cosa u otra te va mejor te va peor
in my case I do not consider myself a bad
en mi caso yo no Considero que sea mala
streamer, on the contrary, I think I entertain
streamer al revés yo creo que entretengo
quite a bit, within reason, like
bastante dentro de lo que cabe así como
for example, I go to other channels and
yo por ejemplo entro en otros canales y
I see that maybe they are playing a game and they
veo que igual están jugando a un juego y
are like this and suddenly you see that they have
están así y de repente ves que tienen
10,000 K or 10,000 viewers and they are
10.000 K o sea 10.000 viewers y están
like this yes it is true it is entertaining, not
así sí es verdad es es entretenido no
for me it is entertaining, it is what I do, which
para mí entretenido es lo que hago yo
is play while I comment while I make
que es jugar mientras comento mientras
jokes, there are even people who are
hago bromas incluso hay gente que le da
ashamed to be seen on channels
vergüenza que que les vean en canales
with few numbers and I have read this
con pocos números y esto lo he leído yo
on Twitter, I have read on Twitter from
en Twitter yo he leído en Twitter de
people saying that I do not go to that
gente diciendo es que yo no voy a ese
channel because I am ashamed to be seen
canal porque me da vergüenza que me vean
on this bef to Javi Oliveira eh
en este bef a Javi oliveira eh
totally totally bef to Javi
totalmente totalmente bef a Javi
Oliveira literal channel because how is it
oliveira literal canal porque como se
considered a channel that no longer has
considera un canal que ya no tiene
numbers  I'm embarrassed you know that they
números me da vergüenza sabes que me
see me that they see How many numbers does ajit have
vean que vean Cuántos números tiene ajit
How many numbers does ajit have more or less
Cuántos números tiene ajit más o menos
how much does he handle 800 spectators 15 around
cuánto maneja 800 espectadores 15 por
there I don't think not on Twitch TT I mean you're embarrassed
ahí no creo no en Twitch TT o sea te da
that they see that
vergüenza que vean que te entretiene
someone in particular entertains you I had a very
alguien en particular tuve un Boom muy
big boom at that moment I took advantage of it I knew how to
grande en ese momento lo aproveché lo
take advantage of it eh I have not been I have
supe aprovechar eh No he sido no he sido
never been a person who has looked for that
una persona nunca que haya buscado eso
eh Because it has always been like very much about doing
eh Porque siempre ha sido como muy de
my thing, doing my thing and such And I have never
estar a mi rollo a mi bola y tal Y nunca
looked for it if I wanted to look for
lo he buscado sipre si quisiera Buscar
those things right now I wouldn't be here
esas cosas ahora mismo no estaría aquí
eh working on something else I assure you about
eh trabajando otra cosa os lo aseguro lo
the criticism this is to see Paloma urba
de la crítica esta a ver Paloma urba
Paloma but look if arjit is pretty that
Paloma pero fíjate si es guapa arjit que
luar always brings me the gossip of aroyit
luar siempre me trae el salseo de aroyit
because in the end the topics that I deal with
porque al final los temas que yo trato
here are chosen by luare or in other words lu eats
aquí los elige luare o sea luá se come
aroyit's live streams and when aroyit
los directos de aroyit y cuando aroyit
says something half-saucy he takes it and
dice algo medio salseante coge y lo y me
puts it here for me it is or not I mean realize
lo pone aquí es o no sea daros cuenta
that here in the end the topics that
que aquí al final los temas que
we comment on he brings me places Look  boom
comentamos me los trae lugares Mira pum
super simple place Bobby alof I don't even know
super simple lugar Bobby alof no sé ni
who he is or any idea says the most viral fa leck in
quién es ni idea dice el fa leck más
history Okay luar what
viral de de la historia Vale luar qué me
are you putting here [ __ ] they're going to
estás poniendo aquí cabrón que me van a
ban me mar Lucas gorgeous also
banear mar Lucas guapísima también
spectacular okay luares simple luares
espectacular vale luares simp luares
super simple on your Twitter not on my
super simp en tu Twitter no en mi
Twitter it's not there you know why Because I
Twitter no está sabéis por qué Porque
deleted the comment because I said it says the
borré el comentario porque dije dice es
delicious thing is more important, the delicious thing
más importante lo de rico lo de rico
look at it luare luare Look at me if you
míramelo luare luare Mírame si
find it if you find it we'll see if
encuentras si lo encuentras lo vemos si
not I'm going because I'm hungry I don't see I'm going to
no me voy que tengo hambre que no vea me
24 hours Look at me that
voy a ir al 24 horas Mírame eso luar de
delicious luar look at everyone
rico mira todo el mundo dándole las
thanking luar luare Thank you thank you
gracias a luar luare Gracias gracias
thank you luar We love you no eh Look
gracias luar Te queremos no eh Mira
check if there's something about that delicious thing and if
velar si hay algo de lo de ricoy si es
what they're telling me is true and yesterday
verdad lo que me están diciendo y ayer
they put in the chat that jut
nos pusieron en el chat que el jut se
had turned green to gref Look to see if it
había puesto verde a gref Mira a ver si
's true It's logical to get involved because let's see I
es verdad Es lógico meterse porque a ver
didn't get involved eh I didn't get involved Javi the diet
no me metí eh No me metí Javi la dieta
I'm already going to Thailand what does it matter already the
ya me voy a Tailandia qué más da ya la
diet I'm already going to Thailand had to go
dieta ya me voy a Tailandia había pasar
hungry no  I'm going to eat with her physique
hambre no voy a comer con su físico
because the girl doesn't seem
porque a mí la chavala no me pare nada
ugly to me at all, I mean, I think she's pretty but I don't think she
fea o sea me parece guapa pero no creo
knows so little about fashion that she doesn't know how to
que sabe tan poco de moda que no se sabe
take advantage of herself, I mean, what's
sacar partido a sí misma o sea lo que lo
happening to her is that she's pretty but she doesn't
que le pasa es que es guapa pero no se
take advantage of herself because she has a cer cer
saca partido porque tiene cer cer cer
cer sense of what fashion is or
cer sentido de de lo que es la moda o o
at least not fashion but taste the thing is
por lo menos no la moda sino el gusto es
that her criticism was more like a roll
que su crítica fue más en plan rollo
looking at what we do on tele5 we talk about
mirando que hacemos en tele5 hablamos de
youtubers Come see us No, what I
youtubers Venid a vernos No yo lo que
think is in a roll like What are
creo es en plan rollo Qué les interesa a
young people interested in today and what what
los jóvenes de hoy en día y qué qué Por
Why do they have so many Ah, the thing about tele5 they were
qué tienen tantos Ah lo de tele5 tenían
right and nothing happens in the end it's a
la razón y no pasa nada al final es una
viral thing it's Commented and and that's
cosa viral se Comenta y y ya
enough
vale
[Music]
[Música]
and
y